<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.openhabittracker.OpenHabitTracker</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>OpenHabitTracker</name>
  <summary>Take notes, plan tasks, track habits</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Notizen, Aufgaben und Gewohnheiten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Notas, tareas y hábitos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zapiski, naloge in navade</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Notes, tâches et habitudes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Notas, tarefas e hábitos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Note, compiti e abitudini</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">メモ・タスク・習慣管理</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">笔记、任务与习惯</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">메모, 할 일, 습관</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Notities, taken en gewoontes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Noter, opgaver og vaner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="no">Notater, oppgaver og vaner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Anteckningar, uppgifter och vanor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Muistiinpanot, tehtävät ja tavat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Notatki, zadania i nawyki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Poznámky, úkoly a návyky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Poznámky, úlohy a návyky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Bilješke, zadaci i navike</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Beleške, zadaci i navike</summary>
  <developer id="net.openhabittracker">
    <name>Jinjinov</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Take Markdown notes, plan tasks, and track habits - with native apps for Windows, Linux, Android, iOS and macOS, plus a web app. Free, ad-free, and open source. No account needed: all your data stays on your device.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Markdown-Notizen schreiben, Aufgaben planen und Gewohnheiten verfolgen - mit nativen Apps für Windows, Linux, Android, iOS und macOS sowie als Web-App. Kostenlos, werbefrei und Open Source. Kein Konto nötig: Alle Daten bleiben auf deinem Gerät.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Toma notas Markdown, planifica tareas y sigue tus hábitos - con aplicaciones nativas para Windows, Linux, Android, iOS y macOS, además de una versión web. Gratis, sin anuncios y de código abierto. Sin cuenta: todos tus datos se quedan en tu dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Piši zapiske v Markdownu, načrtuj naloge in sledi navadam - z izvornimi aplikacijami za Windows, Linux, Android, iOS in macOS ter spletno aplikacijo. Brezplačno, brez oglasov in odprtokodno. Brez računa: vsi podatki ostanejo na tvoji napravi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Prenez des notes Markdown, planifiez vos tâches et suivez vos habitudes - avec des applications natives pour Windows, Linux, Android, iOS et macOS, plus une application web. Gratuit, sans publicité et open source. Aucun compte requis : toutes vos données restent sur votre appareil.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Tome notas em Markdown, planeie tarefas e acompanhe hábitos - com aplicações nativas para Windows, Linux, Android, iOS e macOS, além de uma aplicação web. Gratuito, sem anúncios e open source. Sem conta: todos os dados ficam no seu dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Prendi note in Markdown, pianifica i compiti e monitora le abitudini - con app native per Windows, Linux, Android, iOS e macOS, più un'app web. Gratis, senza pubblicità e open source. Nessun account: tutti i dati restano sul tuo dispositivo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Markdownでメモを取り、タスクを計画し、習慣を記録できます。Windows、Linux、Android、iOS、macOS向けのネイティブアプリとWebアプリを提供。無料・広告なし・オープンソース。アカウント不要で、データはすべて端末に保存されます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">用 Markdown 记笔记、规划任务、培养习惯,提供 Windows、Linux、Android、iOS、macOS 原生应用及网页版。免费、无广告、开源。无需账户,所有数据保存在你的设备上。</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Markdown으로 메모하고, 할 일을 계획하고, 습관을 기록하세요. Windows, Linux, Android, iOS, macOS용 네이티브 앱과 웹 앱을 제공합니다. 무료, 광고 없음, 오픈소스. 계정이 필요 없으며 모든 데이터는 기기에 저장됩니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Maak Markdown-notities, plan taken en volg gewoontes - met native apps voor Windows, Linux, Android, iOS en macOS, plus een webapp. Gratis, reclamevrij en open source. Geen account nodig: al je gegevens blijven op je apparaat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Tag Markdown-noter, planlæg opgaver og følg vaner - med native apps til Windows, Linux, Android, iOS og macOS samt en webapp. Gratis, reklamefri og open source. Ingen konto: alle dine data bliver på din enhed.</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">Ta Markdown-notater, planlegg oppgaver og følg vaner - med native apper for Windows, Linux, Android, iOS og macOS, pluss en webapp. Gratis, reklamefri og åpen kildekode. Ingen konto: alle dataene dine blir på enheten din.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Skriv Markdown-anteckningar, planera uppgifter och följ vanor - med appar för Windows, Linux, Android, iOS och macOS samt en webbapp. Gratis, reklamfri och öppen källkod. Inget konto behövs: all din data stannar på din enhet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kirjoita Markdown-muistiinpanoja, suunnittele tehtäviä ja seuraa tapoja - natiivisovellukset Windowsille, Linuxille, Androidille, iOS:lle ja macOS:lle sekä verkkosovellus. Ilmainen, mainokseton ja avointa lähdekoodia. Ei tiliä: kaikki tietosi pysyvät laitteellasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Twórz notatki w Markdownie, planuj zadania i śledź nawyki - z natywnymi aplikacjami na Windows, Linux, Android, iOS i macOS oraz aplikacją webową. Za darmo, bez reklam i open source. Bez konta: wszystkie dane zostają na Twoim urządzeniu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Pište poznámky v Markdownu, plánujte úkoly a sledujte návyky - s nativními aplikacemi pro Windows, Linux, Android, iOS a macOS a webovou aplikací. Zdarma, bez reklam a open source. Bez účtu: všechna data zůstávají ve vašem zařízení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Píšte poznámky v Markdowne, plánujte úlohy a sledujte návyky - s natívnymi aplikáciami pre Windows, Linux, Android, iOS a macOS a webovou aplikáciou. Zadarmo, bez reklám a open source. Bez účtu: všetky dáta zostávajú vo vašom zariadení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Pišite Markdown bilješke, planirajte zadatke i pratite navike - s izvornim aplikacijama za Windows, Linux, Android, iOS i macOS te web-aplikacijom. Besplatno, bez oglasa i otvorenog koda. Bez računa: svi podaci ostaju na vašem uređaju.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Pišite Markdown beleške, planirajte zadatke i pratite navike - sa izvornim aplikacijama za Windows, Linux, Android, iOS i macOS i veb-aplikacijom. Besplatno, bez reklama i otvorenog koda. Bez naloga: svi podaci ostaju na vašem uređaju.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Notes with full Markdown support</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Notizen mit voller Markdown-Unterstützung</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Notas con soporte completo de Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zapiski s polno podporo za Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Notes avec prise en charge complète de Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Notas com suporte completo de Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Note con pieno supporto Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">Markdown完全対応のメモ</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">完整支持 Markdown 的笔记</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Markdown을 완벽 지원하는 메모</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Notities met volledige Markdown-ondersteuning</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Noter med fuld Markdown-understøttelse</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Notater med full Markdown-støtte</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anteckningar med fullt Markdown-stöd</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Muistiinpanot täydellä Markdown-tuella</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Notatki z pełną obsługą Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Poznámky s plnou podporou Markdownu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Poznámky s plnou podporou Markdownu</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Bilješke s punom podrškom za Markdown</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Beleške s punom podrškom za Markdown</li>
      <li>Tasks with planned dates, duration and time tracking</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aufgaben mit Terminen, Dauer und Zeiterfassung</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Tareas con fechas planificadas, duración y registro de tiempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Naloge z načrtovanimi datumi, trajanjem in merjenjem časa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Tâches avec dates planifiées, durée et suivi du temps</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Tarefas com datas planeadas, duração e registo de tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Compiti con date pianificate, durata e tracciamento del tempo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">予定日・所要時間・時間記録に対応したタスク</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">支持计划日期、时长和时间记录的任务</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">계획 날짜, 소요 시간, 시간 기록을 지원하는 할 일</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Taken met geplande datums, duur en tijdregistratie</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Opgaver med planlagte datoer, varighed og tidsregistrering</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Oppgaver med planlagte datoer, varighet og tidsregistrering</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Uppgifter med planerade datum, varaktighet och tidsregistrering</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tehtävät suunnitelluilla päivillä, kestolla ja ajanseurannalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zadania z planowanymi datami, czasem trwania i rejestracją czasu</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Úkoly s plánovanými daty, dobou trvání a měřením času</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Úlohy s plánovanými dátumami, trvaním a meraním času</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Zadaci s planiranim datumima, trajanjem i praćenjem vremena</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Zadaci s planiranim datumima, trajanjem i praćenjem vremena</li>
      <li>Habits with flexible repeat intervals - track repetitions, time or quantity</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Gewohnheiten mit flexiblen Wiederholungsintervallen - erfasst als Wiederholungen, Zeit oder Menge</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Hábitos con intervalos de repetición flexibles - registra repeticiones, tiempo o cantidad</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Navade s prilagodljivimi intervali ponavljanja - beleži ponovitve, čas ali količino</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Habitudes avec intervalles de répétition flexibles - suivies en répétitions, temps ou quantité</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Hábitos com intervalos de repetição flexíveis - registados como repetições, tempo ou quantidade</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Abitudini con intervalli di ripetizione flessibili - registrate come ripetizioni, tempo o quantità</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">柔軟な繰り返し間隔を持つ習慣(回数・時間・数量で記録)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">重复间隔灵活的习惯,可按次数、时间或数量记录</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">유연한 반복 간격의 습관, 횟수·시간·수량으로 기록</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gewoontes met flexibele herhaalintervallen - bijgehouden als herhalingen, tijd of hoeveelheid</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Vaner med fleksible gentagelsesintervaller - registreret som gentagelser, tid eller mængde</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Vaner med fleksible gjentakelsesintervaller - registrert som repetisjoner, tid eller mengde</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Vanor med flexibla upprepningsintervall - registrerade som repetitioner, tid eller mängd</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tavat joustavilla toistoväleillä - kirjaa toistoina, aikana tai määränä</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Nawyki z elastycznymi odstępami powtarzania - zapisywane jako powtórzenia, czas lub ilość</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Návyky s flexibilními intervaly opakování - zaznamenávané jako opakování, čas nebo množství</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Návyky s flexibilnými intervalmi opakovania - zaznamenávané ako opakovania, čas alebo množstvo</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Navike s fleksibilnim intervalima ponavljanja - bilježe se kao ponavljanja, vrijeme ili količina</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Navike s fleksibilnim intervalima ponavljanja - beleže se kao ponavljanja, vreme ili količina</li>
      <li>Checklist sub-items on both tasks and habits</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Checklisten-Unterpunkte für Aufgaben und Gewohnheiten</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Sublistas de verificación en tareas y hábitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Kontrolni seznami s podtočkami pri nalogah in navadah</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Sous-éléments de type checklist pour les tâches et les habitudes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Subitens de lista de verificação em tarefas e hábitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Sotto-elementi checklist per compiti e abitudini</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">タスクにも習慣にも使えるチェックリスト項目</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">任务和习惯都支持清单子项</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">할 일과 습관 모두에서 쓰는 체크리스트 하위 항목</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Checklist-subitems voor taken én gewoontes</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Tjekliste-underpunkter på både opgaver og vaner</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Sjekkliste-underpunkter på både oppgaver og vaner</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Checklistor med delmoment på både uppgifter och vanor</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tarkistuslistan alakohdat sekä tehtävissä että tavoissa</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podpunkty listy kontrolnej w zadaniach i nawykach</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podúkoly (checklisty) u úkolů i návyků</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podúlohy (checklisty) pri úlohách aj návykoch</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Podstavke popisa (checkliste) na zadacima i navikama</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Podstavke liste (čekliste) na zadacima i navikama</li>
      <li>Categories, colors, priorities, search, filters and sorting - for notes, tasks and habits</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kategorien, Farben, Prioritäten, Suche, Filter und Sortierung - für Notizen, Aufgaben und Gewohnheiten</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Categorías, colores, prioridades, búsqueda, filtros y ordenación - para notas, tareas y hábitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Kategorije, barve, prioritete, iskanje, filtri in razvrščanje - za zapiske, naloge in navade</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Catégories, couleurs, priorités, recherche, filtres et tri - pour les notes, les tâches et les habitudes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Categorias, cores, prioridades, pesquisa, filtros e ordenação - para notas, tarefas e hábitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Categorie, colori, priorità, ricerca, filtri e ordinamento - per note, compiti e abitudini</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">カテゴリ・色・優先度・検索・フィルター・並べ替えをメモ・タスク・習慣すべてで</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">分类、颜色、优先级、搜索、筛选和排序,笔记、任务、习惯通用</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">카테고리, 색상, 우선순위, 검색, 필터, 정렬을 메모·할 일·습관 모두에</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Categorieën, kleuren, prioriteiten, zoeken, filters en sorteren - voor notities, taken en gewoontes</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Kategorier, farver, prioriteter, søgning, filtre og sortering - for noter, opgaver og vaner</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Kategorier, farger, prioriteter, søk, filtre og sortering - for notater, oppgaver og vaner</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kategorier, färger, prioriteter, sökning, filter och sortering - för anteckningar, uppgifter och vanor</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kategoriat, värit, prioriteetit, haku, suodattimet ja lajittelu - muistiinpanoille, tehtäville ja tavoille</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kategorie, kolory, priorytety, wyszukiwanie, filtry i sortowanie - dla notatek, zadań i nawyków</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Kategorie, barvy, priority, hledání, filtry a řazení - pro poznámky, úkoly i návyky</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Kategórie, farby, priority, hľadanie, filtre a triedenie - pre poznámky, úlohy aj návyky</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Kategorije, boje, prioriteti, pretraživanje, filtri i sortiranje - za bilješke, zadatke i navike</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Kategorije, boje, prioriteti, pretraga, filteri i sortiranje - za beleške, zadatke i navike</li>
      <li>All data is stored locally on your device</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Alle Daten werden lokal auf deinem Gerät gespeichert</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Todos los datos se guardan localmente en tu dispositivo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vsi podatki so shranjeni lokalno na tvoji napravi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Toutes les données sont stockées localement sur votre appareil</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Todos os dados são guardados localmente no seu dispositivo</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Tutti i dati sono salvati localmente sul tuo dispositivo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">すべてのデータは端末内にローカル保存</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">所有数据本地保存在你的设备上</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">모든 데이터는 기기에 로컬로 저장됩니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Alle gegevens worden lokaal op je apparaat opgeslagen</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Alle data gemmes lokalt på din enhed</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Alle data lagres lokalt på enheten din</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">All data sparas lokalt på din enhet</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kaikki tiedot tallennetaan paikallisesti laitteellesi</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wszystkie dane są zapisywane lokalnie na Twoim urządzeniu</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Všechna data se ukládají lokálně ve vašem zařízení</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Všetky dáta sa ukladajú lokálne vo vašom zariadení</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Svi podaci spremaju se lokalno na vašem uređaju</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Svi podaci se čuvaju lokalno na vašem uređaju</li>
      <li>Export and import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Export und Import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Exporta e importa: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izvoz in uvoz: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Export et import : Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Exportação e importação: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Esporta e importa: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">エクスポート/インポート:Markdown、JSON、YAML、TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">导出/导入:Markdown、JSON、YAML、TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">내보내기/가져오기: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Exporteren en importeren: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Eksport og import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Eksport og import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Export och import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vienti ja tuonti: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Eksport i import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Export a import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Export a import: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Izvoz i uvoz: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Izvoz i uvoz: Markdown, JSON, YAML, TSV</li>
      <li>Import your notes from Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Importiere deine Notizen aus Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importa tus notas desde Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Uvozi zapiske iz Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Importez vos notes depuis Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importe as suas notas do Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importa le tue note da Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">Google Keepからメモをインポート</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">从 Google Keep 导入笔记</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Google Keep에서 메모 가져오기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeer je notities uit Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Importér dine noter fra Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Importer notatene dine fra Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importera dina anteckningar från Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tuo muistiinpanosi Google Keepistä</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Importuj notatki z Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Import poznámek z Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Import poznámok z Google Keep</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Uvezite bilješke iz Google Keepa</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Uvezite beleške iz Google Keepa</li>
      <li>Optional sync: host the free Docker image on your own server and every app, desktop or mobile, can log in and sync</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Optionale Synchronisierung: Hoste das kostenlose Docker-Image auf deinem eigenen Server - jede App, ob Desktop oder Mobil, kann sich anmelden und synchronisieren</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Sincronización opcional: aloja la imagen Docker gratuita en tu propio servidor y cualquier aplicación, de escritorio o móvil, puede iniciar sesión y sincronizarse</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Neobvezna sinhronizacija: gosti brezplačno sliko Docker na svojem strežniku in vsaka aplikacija, namizna ali mobilna, se lahko prijavi in sinhronizira</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Synchronisation optionnelle : hébergez l'image Docker gratuite sur votre propre serveur et chaque application, bureau ou mobile, peut se connecter et se synchroniser</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Sincronização opcional: aloje a imagem Docker gratuita no seu próprio servidor e qualquer aplicação, de secretária ou móvel, pode iniciar sessão e sincronizar</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Sincronizzazione opzionale: ospita l'immagine Docker gratuita sul tuo server e ogni app, desktop o mobile, può accedere e sincronizzarsi</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">任意の同期:無料のDockerイメージを自分のサーバーでホストすれば、デスクトップ版もモバイル版もログインして同期できます</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可选同步:在自己的服务器上运行免费 Docker 镜像,桌面和移动端应用都能登录同步</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">선택적 동기화: 무료 Docker 이미지를 내 서버에 올리면 데스크톱과 모바일 앱 모두 로그인하여 동기화할 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Optionele synchronisatie: host de gratis Docker-image op je eigen server en elke app, desktop of mobiel, kan inloggen en synchroniseren</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Valgfri synkronisering: host det gratis Docker-image på din egen server, og alle apps, desktop eller mobil, kan logge ind og synkronisere</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Valgfri synkronisering: kjør det gratis Docker-imaget på din egen server, og alle appene, desktop eller mobil, kan logge inn og synkronisere</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Valfri synkronisering: kör den gratis Docker-avbilden på din egen server så kan alla appar, dator eller mobil, logga in och synkronisera</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Valinnainen synkronointi: aja ilmainen Docker-levykuva omalla palvelimellasi, niin jokainen sovellus, työpöytä tai mobiili, voi kirjautua ja synkronoida</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Opcjonalna synchronizacja: uruchom darmowy obraz Dockera na własnym serwerze, a każda aplikacja, desktopowa czy mobilna, może się zalogować i synchronizować</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Volitelná synchronizace: provozujte bezplatný Docker image na vlastním serveru a každá aplikace, desktopová i mobilní, se může přihlásit a synchronizovat</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Voliteľná synchronizácia: prevádzkujte bezplatný Docker image na vlastnom serveri a každá aplikácia, desktopová aj mobilná, sa môže prihlásiť a synchronizovať</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Neobavezna sinkronizacija: pokrenite besplatni Docker image na vlastitom poslužitelju i svaka aplikacija, stolna ili mobilna, može se prijaviti i sinkronizirati</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Opciona sinhronizacija: pokrenite besplatni Docker image na sopstvenom serveru i svaka aplikacija, desktop ili mobilna, može da se prijavi i sinhronizuje</li>
      <li>26 themes with dark and light mode</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">26 Themes mit Dunkel- und Hellmodus</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">26 temas con modo oscuro y claro</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">26 tem s temnim in svetlim načinom</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">26 thèmes avec mode sombre et clair</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">26 temas com modo escuro e claro</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">26 temi con modalità scura e chiara</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">ダーク/ライト対応の26種類のテーマ</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">26 款主题,支持深色和浅色模式</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다크/라이트 모드를 지원하는 26가지 테마</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">26 thema's met donkere en lichte modus</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">26 temaer med mørk og lys tilstand</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">26 temaer med mørk og lys modus</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">26 teman med mörkt och ljust läge</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">26 teemaa tummalla ja vaalealla tilalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">26 motywów z trybem ciemnym i jasnym</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">26 motivů s tmavým a světlým režimem</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">26 tém s tmavým a svetlým režimom</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">26 tema s tamnim i svijetlim načinom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">26 tema s tamnim i svetlim režimom</li>
      <li>Customizable UI - show or hide almost every element</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anpassbare Oberfläche - fast jedes Element lässt sich ein- oder ausblenden</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Interfaz personalizable - muestra u oculta casi cualquier elemento</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prilagodljiv vmesnik - skoraj vsak element lahko skriješ ali pokažeš</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Interface personnalisable - affichez ou masquez presque chaque élément</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Interface personalizável - mostre ou oculte quase todos os elementos</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Interfaccia personalizzabile - mostra o nascondi quasi ogni elemento</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">カスタマイズ可能なUI(ほぼすべての要素を表示/非表示)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可定制界面,几乎每个元素都能显示或隐藏</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">커스터마이징 가능한 UI, 거의 모든 요소를 표시하거나 숨길 수 있음</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Aanpasbare interface - toon of verberg bijna elk element</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Tilpasselig brugerflade - vis eller skjul næsten alle elementer</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Tilpassbart grensesnitt - vis eller skjul nesten alle elementer</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsbart gränssnitt - visa eller dölj nästan varje element</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Mukautettava käyttöliittymä - näytä tai piilota lähes jokainen elementti</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Konfigurowalny interfejs - pokaż lub ukryj niemal każdy element</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Přizpůsobitelné rozhraní - téměř každý prvek lze zobrazit nebo skrýt</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Prispôsobiteľné rozhranie - takmer každý prvok možno zobraziť alebo skryť</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Prilagodljivo sučelje - prikažite ili sakrijte gotovo svaki element</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Prilagodljiv interfejs - prikažite ili sakrijte gotovo svaki element</li>
      <li>Available in 20 languages</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Verfügbar in 20 Sprachen</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Disponible en 20 idiomas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Na voljo v 20 jezikih</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Disponible en 20 langues</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Disponível em 20 idiomas</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Disponibile in 20 lingue</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">20言語に対応</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">支持 20 种语言</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">20개 언어 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beschikbaar in 20 talen</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Fås på 20 sprog</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Tilgjengelig på 20 språk</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tillgänglig på 20 språk</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Saatavilla 20 kielellä</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dostępna w 20 językach</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">K dispozici ve 20 jazycích</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">K dispozícii v 20 jazykoch</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Dostupno na 20 jezika</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Dostupno na 20 jezika</li>
      <li>Keyboard navigation and screen reader support</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Tastaturnavigation und Screenreader-Unterstützung</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Navegación por teclado y soporte para lectores de pantalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Navigacija s tipkovnico in podpora bralnikom zaslona</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Navigation au clavier et prise en charge des lecteurs d'écran</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação por teclado e suporte para leitores de ecrã</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Navigazione da tastiera e supporto per screen reader</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">キーボード操作とスクリーンリーダーに対応</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">支持键盘操作和屏幕阅读器</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">키보드 탐색 및 스크린 리더 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Toetsenbordnavigatie en schermlezerondersteuning</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Tastaturnavigation og skærmlæserunderstøttelse</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Tastaturnavigasjon og skjermleserstøtte</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tangentbordsnavigering och skärmläsarstöd</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Näppäimistönavigointi ja ruudunlukijatuki</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Nawigacja klawiaturą i obsługa czytników ekranu</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Ovládání klávesnicí a podpora čteček obrazovky</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ovládanie klávesnicou a podpora čítačiek obrazovky</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Navigacija tipkovnicom i podrška za čitače zaslona</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Navigacija tastaturom i podrška za čitače ekrana</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.openhabittracker.OpenHabitTracker.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>OpenHT</binary>
  </provides>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>Open source</keyword>
    <keyword>Habit tracker</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <icon type="stock">net.openhabittracker.OpenHabitTracker</icon>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <url type="homepage">https://openhabittracker.net</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/Jinjinov/OpenHabitTracker</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/Jinjinov/OpenHabitTracker</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/Jinjinov/OpenHabitTracker/issues</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <video codec="vp9" width="1920" height="1080">https://openhabittracker.net/videos/desktop-main.webm</video>
      <caption>Notes, Tasks, Habits</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <video codec="vp9" width="1920" height="1080">https://openhabittracker.net/videos/desktop-sidebar.webm</video>
      <caption>Search, Settings</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_1_settings.png</image>
      <caption>Settings</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_2_note.png</image>
      <caption>Note</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_3_notes.png</image>
      <caption>Notes</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_4_task.png</image>
      <caption>Task</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_5_tasks.png</image>
      <caption>Tasks</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_6_habit.png</image>
      <caption>Habit</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_7_habits.png</image>
      <caption>Habits</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://openhabittracker.net/images/desktop_8_backup.png</image>
      <caption>Backup</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.2.2" date="2026-05-25">
      <description>
        <p>Added current and best streak in habits</p>
        <p>Added three habit display modes: Repetitions, Time, Quantity</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.1" date="2026-04-04">
      <description>
        <p>Added Shift+Tab and multi-line Tab</p>
        <p>Added GET query endpoints with URL filter parameters (Docker/Web API)</p>
        <p>Added habit start date</p>
        <p>Added "under x%" habit interval ratio filter</p>
        <p>Fixed collapse toggle not refreshing sibling pages in Home</p>
        <p>Fixed new note / task / habit with category appearing twice in grouped view</p>
        <p>Fixed Add new habit in PWA</p>
        <p>Fixed DB migration hang</p>
        <p>Fixed Edit note</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.8" date="2026-03-27">
      <description>
        <p>Added category-grouped view for notes, tasks, habits</p>
        <p>Added "and / or" completion rule per category</p>
        <p>Added completion status per category group</p>
        <p>Added last done time per category group</p>
        <p>Added arrow key navigation for the guided tour</p>
        <p>Fixed Empty trash</p>
        <p>Fixed Rename category</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.7" date="2026-03-21">
      <description>
        <p>Added weekly recap / stats for notes, tasks, habits</p>
        <p>Added arrow key navigation for the menu</p>
        <p>Added arrow key navigation for the calendar</p>
        <p>Added focus management</p>
        <p>Improved keyboard navigation</p>
        <p>Fixed app icon in Linux</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.6" date="2026-03-11">
      <description>
        <p>Added 16 new languages: French, Portuguese, Italian, Japanese, Chinese, Korean, Dutch, Danish, Norwegian, Swedish, Finnish, Polish, Slovak, Czech, Croatian, Serbian</p>
        <p>Improved accessibility: navigation landmarks, ARIA labels, keyboard navigation</p>
        <p>Fixed Google Keep import</p>
        <p>Fixed date comparison bug</p>
        <p>Fixed login session expiring on Docker VM suspension</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.5" date="2026-02-14">
      <description>
        <p>Replaced "X" with "Close"</p>
        <p>Search icon is now a toggle</p>
        <p>Increased default vertical margin</p>
        <p>Use background color for the whole note / task / habit</p>
        <p>Added "Show priority" setting</p>
        <p>Added "Show habit statistics" setting</p>
        <p>Added "Show category" setting</p>
        <p>Increased Notes / Tasks / Habits font size</p>
        <p>Fixed a bug where priority was not displayed properly</p>
        <p>Fixed a bug where there was not enough room for the small calendar</p>
        <p>Fixed a bug where the keyboard covered text input on Android</p>
        <p>Use Gnome 49 in Flatpack</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.4" date="2025-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed Flatpak and Snapcraft folder permissions</p>
        <p>Fixed updating From and To time in Habit</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.3" date="2025-03-30">
      <description>
        <p>Setting to hide completed tasks</p>
        <p>Improved filters</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.2" date="2025-03-03">
      <description>
        <p>Replaced help with a guided tour</p>
        <p>Added a Docker image for online sync</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.1" date="2025-02-02">
      <description>
        <p>Fixed export of items with no category</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.0" date="2025-01-13">
      <description>
        <p>Improved UI:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>display a welcome note instead of examples when user opens the app for the first time</li>
          <li>added a lot of new icons</li>
          <li>completely new Help screen</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2024-12-31">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release of OpenHabitTracker.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
